worldofbrowsers.com 2018-03-21

# Privacy Policy & Affiliate Disclosure

[World of Browsers](http://worldofbrowsers.com/) is committed to protecting the privacy of online users. This document outlines our technology and the practices we use to collect information.

## What information we collect

World of Browsers does not collect any personally identifiable information (PII) from users. Term “PII” generally refers to information such as an individual’s name, mailing address, phone number or email address.

World of Browsers provides its users with a range of articles published via its website. Through the use of cookies, we collect anonymous usage statistics to improve our website and offer better user experience. These are industry standard technologies used by many major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. Information that is collected may include: session data, geography, browser information, IP address, operating system type.

## Using cookies

A cookie is a small text file placed onto your device that enables some [World of Browsers](http://worldofbrowsers.com/) features and functionality to enhance your user experience. For example, cookies help us to identify your device and offer you the latest article you haven’t seen yet or to figure out how many new visitors we get each month. Cookies also make it simple for you to share interesting content on our website and help us serve relevant ads to you. In a nutshell, they contain information about the use of your device but don’t include personal information about you (for example, they don’t store your name).

## Children’s online privacy

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Information security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against the unauthorized access to, retention of, and disclosure of data. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic, and management activities required to protect data integrity, access, and use. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential information.

Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers, no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your data at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

## Spam and email lists

We do not intentionally send unsolicited email messages that could be construed as spam.

## Affiliate disclosure

In accordance with FTC guidelines, [World of Browsers](http://worldofbrowsers.com/) has financial relationships with some of the products and services mentioned on this website, and World of Browsers may be compensated if consumers choose to click these links in our content and ultimately sign up for them.

## Contact us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or anything else, you may contact us using [this form.](http://wordlofbrowsers.com/contact-us)
